Sanskar Agrawal

Web Developer | IOT Researcher | ML Enthusiast

I currently have experience in Web Development/Design and some using Futter. I have many personal projects in Web Development and have other projects with Webarch Club. I want to focus on having a career in Data Science. I want to have Masters Degree in Data Science in an Ivy League University.

94

sanskarag23@gmail.com

Bilaspur, India

in linkedin.com/in/sanskar-a-9b2827113

instagram.com/sanskarag23

8839327585

novoarte.net/

github.com/Sanskarag123

EDUCATION

B.Tech

SRM Institute Of Science And Technology

07/2018 - Present

Courses

 Computer Science Engineering

CBSE

KV, Bilaspur

06/2016 - 06/2018 Bilaspur, Chattisgarh

Courses

PhysicsChemistry

- Maths - CS

WORK EXPERIENCE

Co-Founder & Technical Head

Novoartè 🗷

10/2019 - Present

We are a team of design innovators from all aspects of domain including technical and non-technical. We hope to achieve and penetrate the design culture of students and from working members from all aspects of life.

Contact: Adhiraj Bhagawati - 6000587986

Angular Developer CollegeStop Ventures

05/2020 - 07/2020

This was company aimed to build jobs recruitment site, to ease other companies recruit employees.

Achievements/Tasks

- Created most of the front end of the site - jobreferi.com

Web Developer

Webarch 2

03/2019 - 03/2020

We do research & build great products. We also provide a variety of services to our clients.

Achievements/Tasks

- Worked on Staffquarters website of SRM
- Contributed to Enigmatic Plodder Team's website.

SKILLS



GROUP PROJECTS

Gocotracker

url - gocotracker.heroku.com

04/2020

Tasks/Achievements

- IBM special track Winners of Hackon hackathon
- Recorgnized among some of top teams in MJFCOVID19 hackathon

PlacementPortal

SRMIST

08/2020 - Present

Tasks/Achievements

- This site is made using mean stack.
- It tracks the information of student placements and broadcasts important details regarding placements.

SRMIEC website

srmiec.co.in

02/2020 - 03/2020

Srm Staffquarters SRM

07/2019 - 09/2019

Description

It is website for SRM staffs to apply for quarters, and various other services

WORK EXPERIENCE

Backend Developer SRM Industrial Energy Conference

It is a team which conduct and manages industrial conferences at campus . Students from all domains and college participates

Achievements/Tasks

- Built Backend SRMIEC website using PHP and Ajax

Research Associate

02/2020 - Present

INDIA'S FIRST MULTI-DISCIPINARY UNDERGRADUATE RESEARCH LAB with over \$10,000 funding. Research in: Artificial Intelligence, Game Development and Extended Reality, Electrical Systems and Internet of Things and Blockchain and Cryptography.

CERTIFICATES

Tensorflow Professional Certificate (06/2020 - Present)

This course consists of all tensorflow services, how they work, how to implement them and to optimize ml algorithms.

Neural Networks and Deep Learning (04/2020 - 05/2020)

AWS Fundamentals (06/2020 - 07/2020)

In this course we learn about the basic aws services and how to use

JavaScript Development (05/2019 - 06/2019)

Natural Language Processing in TensorFlow (07/2020 - 08/2020)

SQL for DataScience (05/2020 - 06/2020)

Introduction to TensorFlow for Artificial Intelligence. Machine Learning, and Deep Learning (01/2020 - 02/2020) 🗷

In this course we learn the basics of Tensorflow . Basics concepts of neural network. Building image classifiers. Training neural network. Using image Generators, validators and many more.

The Complete 2020 Flutter Development Bootcamp with Dart (03/2020 - 04/2020)

This course provides knowledge and practice about flutter till intermediate level.

Pandas Foundation (02/2020)

Intermediate importing Data in Python (12/2020)

specialization. Its covers the importing of Data from Ineternet and various other kind of file types.

VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE

Aarush SRM Volunteer

Aarush

09/2018 - 10/2018

NSS Volunteer (Awareness Campaign About Plastic Use) SRM

01/2019 - 05/2019

PERSONAL PROJECTS

Personal bot (06/2020 - Present)

- It is made using tensorflow, and web scrapping tools.
- It connect to meeting automatically on schedule time.
- Keeps track of all ongoing processes and closes them automatically.
- Able to control most of my activities on pc with phone which has app made in flutter.

Amazon price tracking extension (07/2020 - 09/2020)

This is the extension to track the price of particular product in

Ecommerce Website (04/2020 - 05/2020)

- This is a simple ecommerce website for selling the things online.
- Its was build on Mean Stack

Front End of Staff-guarters (06/2019 - 07/2019) &

- This website aims on applying for quarters by the the staff and
- There are also options like applying for other services, mainteneance and repair.
- Staff can login by their staff ID and password provided to them by institution

Quiz Creator (12/2019 - 01/2020)

- This webisite is created using MEAN stack.
- This aims on creating quizzes that can only be played by selected inviduals by creater or can done public.
- The points are calculate for each and stored to be reviewed by creator.

Flash Chat (04/2020 - 04/2020)

- This is group messaging app.
- It was built in Flutter with Firebase

SyncMusic (04/2020 - Present)

Its a simple music app with inbuilt many songs.

Library Managment System (03/2020)

- This software aims at organizing books into library.
- This is being built using python and sql.

LANGUAGES

English

Full Professional Proficiency

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

Japanese

Elementary Proficiency

Its is certificate provided by Data Camp as part of their Data Scientist